Guide to Louis Henley Collection
Erie Canal Museum
Louis Henley Collection
1900 - 1923
1906 - 1909
Correspondence and business documents from Louis Henley, owner and boat builder at Phoenix Boat Yard in Phoenix, NY
2 boxes
Henley, Louis
Erie Canal Museum 318 Erie Boulevard East Syracuse, NY 13202
The collection is open for research use.
Louis Henley was the owner of Phoenix Boat Yard in Phoenix NY, where he built, repaired, and launched various types of boats.
Erie Canal (N.Y.); Phoenix (N.Y.)
Correspondence and business documents of Louis Henley, owner of Phoenix Boat Yard, including invoices and receipts for materials purchased, checks, and advertisements. The bulk of the material dates from 1906 to 1909.
- Correspondence
  - Correspondence H-J
    - Correspondence, Ingersoll-Rand Co., 1908 - 1909; Includes items FC 2019.04.01-.06, FC 2019.04.08, FC 2019.04.10-.14 (Box 1, Folder Henley-Ingersoll-Rand Co.)
    - Correspondence, H-J, 1907 - 1909; Correspondence between Louis Henley and various businesses and individuals.; Includes items FC 2019.04.15-.26, FC 2019.04.37, FC 2019.04.39-.42, FC 2019.04.44, FC 2019.04.47-.48 (Box 1, Folder Henley-H-J)
  - Correspondence K-L
    - Correspondence, K-L, 1907 - 1910; Correspondence between Louis Henley and various businesses and individuals.; Includes items FC 2019.04.53, FC 2019.04.63-.64, FC 2019.04.71, FC 2019.04.76-.78, FC 2019.04.86-.88, FC 2019.04.97-.98, FC 2019.04.101-.106 (Box 1, Folder Henley-K-L)
  - Correspondence M-N
    - Correspondence, H.B. McCall, 1909; Correspondence between Louis Henley and H.B. McCall, General Merchandise.; Includes items FC 2019.04.147-152, FC 2019.04.192 (Box 1, Folder Henley-H.B. McCall)
    - Correspondence, R.C. McClure Co., 1908; Correspondence between Louis Henley and the R.C. McClure Co., Plumbers' and Engineers' Supplies.; Includes items FC 2019.04.204, FC 2019.04.206 (Box 1, Folder Henley-R.C. McClure)
    - Correspondence, New York State, 1906 - 1923; Correspondence between Louis Henley and NYS Dept. Public Works, Dept. Labor, and the Comptroller's office.; Includes items FC 2019.04.207-.211, FC 2019.04.213-.215, FC 2019.04.218 (Box 1, Folder Henley-New York State)
    - Correspondence, M-N, 1905 - 1909; Correspondence between Louis Henley and various businesses and individuals.; Includes items FC 2019.04.219, FC 2019.04.221-222, FC 2019.04.224-.225, FC 2019.04.231-.233, FC 2019.04.239-.240, FC 2019.04.242-.243, FC 2019.04.245-.250, FC 2019.04.259-.260, FC 2019.04.262, FC 2019.04.267-.274 (Box 1, Folder Henley-M-N)
  - Correspondence O-P
    - Correspondence, Peck, Duncan W., 1906 - 1909; Correspondence between Louis Henley and Duncan W. Peck.; Includes items FC 2019.04.313-.314, FC 2019.04.318 (Box 1, Folder Henley-Peck, Duncan W.)
    - Correspondence, Post & Henderson Co., 1906 - 1909; Correspondence between Louis Henley and the Post & Henderson Co.; Includes items FC 2019.04.361, FC 2019.04.366, FC 2019.04.374, FC 2019.04.378, FC 2019.04.380, FC 2019.04.382-383 (Box 1, Folder Henley-Post & Henderson Co.)
    - Correspondence, O-P, 1908 - 1910; Correspondence between Louis Henley and various businesses and individuals.; Includes items FC 2019.04.387-.388, FC 2019.04.391-.394, FC 2019.04.396, FC 2019.04.401, FC 2019.04.403-405, FC 2019.04.410-412, FC 2019.04.417, FC 2019.04.419-420, FC 2019.04.435-436 (Box 1, Folder Henley-O-P)
  - Correspondence Q-S
    - Correspondence, Q-S, 1906 - 1910; Correspondence between Louis Henley and various businesses and individuals.; Includes items FC 2019.04.442, FC 2019.04.444-446, FC 2019.04.450-.452, FC 2019.04.456-460, FC 2019.04.468, FC 2019.04.471, FC 2019.04.476-480, FC 2019.04.482, FC 2019.04.489, FC 2019.04.491, FC 2019.04.494-495, FC 2019.04.497-498 (Box 1, Folder Henley-Q-S)
    - Correspondence, Scranton Bolt & Nut Co., 1909; Correspondence between the Scranton Bolt & Nut Co. and Louis Henley.; Includes items FC 2019.04.511, FC 2019.04.518-.519 (Box 1, Folder Henley-Scranton Bolt & Nut Co.)
    - Correspondence, Seneca River Power Co., 1908 - 1910; Correspondence between the Seneca River Power Co. and Louis Henley.; Includes items FC 2019.04.525, FC 2019.04.537, FC 2019.04.552, FC 2019.554-.556, FC 2019.559-.560 (Box 1, Folder Henley-Seneca River Power Co.)
    - Correspondence, Standard Oil Co. of New York, 1908 - 1909; Correspondence between Louis Henley and the Standard Oil Co. of New York.; Includes items FC 2019.04.569, FC 2019.04.576-.584 (Box 1, Folder Henley-Standard Oil Co. of New York)
    - Correspondence, Stewart-Kerbaugh-Shanley Co., 1908 - 1909; Correspondence between Louis Henley and the Stewart-Kerbaugh-Shanley Co.; Includes items FC 2019.04.587-.601, FC 2019.04.603-628, FC 2019.04.630-.636, FC 2019.04.638, FC 2019.04.640-645, FC 2019.04.647-652, FC 2019.04.655-.660 (Box 1, Folder Henley-Stewart-Kerbaugh-Shanley Co.)
    - Correspondence, Syracuse Supply Co., 1907 - 1909; Correspondence between Louis Henley and the Syracuse Supply Co.; Includes items FC 2019.04.675, FC 2019.04.680 (Box 1, Folder Henley-Syracuse Supply Co.)
  - Correspondence T-Z
    - Correspondence, Frank Toomey, 1907 - 1909; Correspondence between Louis Henley and Frank Toomey, Machinery and Supplies of Every Description.; Includes items FC 2019.04.688, FC 2019.04.694-.696 (Box 1, Folder Henley-Frank Toomey)
    - Correspondence, Weed & Co., 1908 - 1909; Correspondence between Louis Henley and Weed & Co., Hardware.; Includes items FC 2019.04.713-.718, FC 2019.04.722, FC 2019.04.726-.727, FC 2019.04.732, FC 2019.04.734-.736, FC 2019.04.742-.744, FC 2019.04.746, FC 2019.04.754 (Box 1, Folder Henley-Weed & Co.)
    - Correspondence, T-Z, 1907 - 1910; Correspondence between Louis Henley and various companies.; Includes items FC 2019.04.757, FC 2019.04.759-.760, FC 2019.04.770-.772, FC 2019.04.779, FC 2019.04.781-.782, FC 2019.04.784-.790, FC 2019.04.792 (Box 1, Box-folder Henley-T-Z)
  - Correspondence-Miscellaneous
    - Correspondence, Miscellaneous, 1909; Correspondence between Louis Henley and various companies and individuals.; Includes items FC 2019.04.805-.808, FC 2019.04.810, FC 2019.04.814-.822, FC 2019.04.841-.845 (Box 1, Folder Henley-Miscellaneous)
  - Correspondence A
    - Correspondence, American Wood Working Machinery Co., 1907; Correspondence between the American Wood Working Machinery Co. and Louis Henley.; Includes item FC 2019.04.847 (Box 2, Folder Henley-American Woodworking Machinery Co.)
    - Correspondence, Atlas Oil Co., 1906 - 1909; Correspondence between the Atlas Oil Co. and Louis Henley.; Includes items FC 2019.04.858, FC 2019.04.863, FC 2019.04.866-867, FC 2019.04.874 (Box 2, Folder Henley-Atlas Oil Co.)
    - Correspondence, A, 1908 - 1910; Correspondence between Louis Henley and various businesses and individuals.; Includes items FC 2019.04.878-.882, FC 2019.04.893-.894, FC 2019.04.898-.899, FC 2019.04.901, FC 2019.04.915-.917 (Box 2, Folder Henley-A)
  - Correspondence B
    - Correspondence, The Bucyrus Co., 1908; Correspondence between Louis Henley and the Bucyrus Co., for whom Henley is building boats.; Includes items FC 2019.04.918-.930 (Box 2, Folder Henley-The Bucyrus Co.)
    - Correspondence, B, 1907 - 1909; Correspondence between Louis Henley and various businesses and individuals.; Includes items FC 2019.04.957, FC 2019.04.959-.963, FC 2019.04.972, FC 2019.04.977, FC 2019.04.980-.983, FC 2019.04.986, FC 2019.04.990-.991, FC 2019.04.993 (Box 2, Folder Henley-B)
  - Correspondence C
    - Correspondence, The Clancy Hardware Co., 1908; Correspondence between Louis Henley and The Clancy Hardware Co.; Includes items FC 2019.04.1076-.1077 (Box 2, Folder Henley-The Clancy Hardware Co.)
    - Correspondence, C, 1907 - 1909; Correspondence between Louis Henley and various businesses and individuals.; Includes items FC 2019.04.1134-.1139, FC 2019.04.1141-.1145, FC 2019.04.1149, FC 2019.04.1152-.1157, FC 2019.04.1159, FC 2019.04.1162-.1165 (Box 2, Folder Henley-C)
  - Correspondence D-G
    - Correspondence, DeGrauw, Aymar & Co., 1908 - 1909; Correspondence between Louis Henley and DeGrauw, Aymar & Co.; Includes items FC 2019.04.1173, FC 2019.04.1183-.1188, FC 2019.04.1190-.1191, FC 2019.04.1193-.1195 (Box 2, Folder Henley-DeGrauw, Aymar & Co.)
    - Correspondence, D-G, 1905 - 1910; Correspondence between Louis Henley and various businesses and individuals.; Includes items FC 2019.04.1205, FC 2019.04.1214, FC 2019.04.1223-.1225, FC 2019.04.1228, FC 2019.04.1230, FC 2019.04.1232, FC 2019.04.1234, FC 2019.04.1245-.1248, FC 2019.04.1250-.1255, FC 2019.04.1257-.1258, FC 2019.04.1260-.1263 FC 2019.04.1267, FC 2019.04.1269-.1270, FC 2019.04.1273-.1274, FC 2019.04.1276-.1277, FC 2019.04.1279-.1285, FC 2019.04.1290-.1297 (Box 2, Folder Henley-D-G)
    - Correspondence, Empire Engineering Corp., 1906 - 1909; Correspondence between Louis Henley and the Empire Engineering Corp., largely regarding boats Henley is building for them.; Includes items FC 2019.04.1300-.1335 (Box 2, Folder Henley-Empire Engineering Corp.)
    - Correspondence, The Fairbanks Co., 1908 - 1910; Correspondence between Louis Henley and The Fairbanks Co., scales, machine tools, and supplies.; Includes items FC 2019.04.1388, FC 2019.04.1392, FC 2019.04.1406, FC 2019.04.1416, FC 2019.04.1422, FC 2019.04.1436, FC 2019.04.1445, FC 2019.04.1447 (Box 2, Folder Henley-The Fairbanks Co.)
    - Correspondence, D.L. Gillespie & Co., 1909; Correspondence between Louis Henley and D.L. Gillespie & Co.; Includes items FC 2019.04.1475-.1479, FC 2019.04.1482, FC 2019.04.1484-.1487 (Box 2, Folder Henley-D.L. Gillespie & Co.)
- Business Documents
  - Business Documents H-J
    - Business Documents, Ingersoll-Rand Co., 1909; Includes items FC 2019.04.07 and FC 2019.04.09; Henley's monthly statement and an invoice from Ingersoll-Rand Co., makers of drills and tools. (Box 1, Folder Henley-Ingersoll-Rand Co.)
    - Business Documents, H-J, 1906 - 1910; Invoices, receipts, and checks from various companies.; Includes items FC 2019.04.27-.35, FC 2019.04.38, FC 2019.04.43, FC 2019.04.45-.46 (Box 1, Folder Henley-H-J)
    - Business Documents, N.A. Hughes, 1906 - 1909; Invoices and receipts from N.A. Hughes to Louis Henley. Checks from Henley to N.A. Hughes.; Includes items FC 2019.04.1490-.1499 (Box 2, Folder Henley-N.A. Hughes)
  - Business Documents K-L
    - Business Documents, K-L, 1906 - 1910; Invoices, receipts, and checks from various businesses.; Includes items FC 2019.04.49-.52, FC 2019.04.54-.62, FC 2019.04.65-.70, FC 2019.04.72-.75, FC 2019.04.79-.85, FC 2019.04.89-.95, FC 2019.04.99-.100 (Box 1, Folder Henley-K-L)
    - Business Documents, J.H. Loomis & Sons, 1905 - 1910; Invoices and receipts from J.H. Loomis & Sons, Planing Mill and Lumber Yard, to Louis Henley, checks from Louis Henley to J.H. Loomis & Sons.; Includes items FC 2019.04.107-.146 (Box 1, Folder Henley-J.H. Loomis & Sons)
  - Business Documents M-N
    - Business Documents, H.B. McCall, 1909; Invoices, receipts, shipping orders and bills of lading from H.B. McCall, General Merchandise.; Includes items FC 2019.04.153-.191, FC 2019.04.193 (Box 1, Folder Henley-H.B. McCall)
    - Business Documents, R.C. McClure Co., 1908 - 1911; Invoices and statements from the R.C. McClure Co., Plumbers' and Engineers' Supplies.; Includes items FC 2019.04.194-.203, FC 2019.04.205 (Box 1, Folder Henley-R.C. McClure Co.)
    - Business Documents, New York State, 1906 - 1910; Receipts from the Comptroller and Collector for payments received from Louis Henley; Includes items FC 2019.04.212, FC 2019.04.216-.217 (Box 1, Folder Henley-New York State)
    - Business Documents, M-N, 1905 - 1911; Invoices, receipts, and checks from and to various businesses and Louis Henley; Includes items FC 2019.04.220, FC 2019.04.223, FC 2019.04.226-.230, FC 2019.04.234-.238, FC 2019.04.241, FC 2019.04.244, FC 2019.04.251-.258, FC 2019.04.261, FC 2019.04.263-.265 (Box 1, Folder Henley-M-N)
  - Business Documents O-P
    - Business Documents, Oswego County Independent Telephone Co., 1909 - 1910; Bills and receipts from the Oswego Independent Telephone Co. to Louis Henley.; Includes items FC 2019.04.275-.301 (Box 1, Folder Henley-Oswego County Independent Telephone Co.)
    - Business Documents, Peck, Duncan W., 1906 - 1909; Invoices from Duncan W. Peck to Louis Henley.; Includes items FC 2019.04.302-312, FC 2019.04.315-.317, FC 2019.04.319-.320 (Box 1, Folder Henley-Peck, Duncan W.)
    - Business Documents, Phoenix Fuel, Light, and Water Co., 1905 - 1909; Monthly statements and Phoenix Fuel, Light and Water Co. to Louis Henley. Checks from Henley to the Co.; Includes items FC 2019.04.321-.347 (Box 1, Folder Henley-Phoenix Fuel, Light, and Water Co.)
    - Business Documents, Post & Henderson Co., 1905 - 1909; Invoices and receipts from Post & Henderson Co., Mfgs. and wholesale dealers in lumber, lath, & shingles, to Louis Henley. Checks from Henley to Post & Henderson Co.; Includes items FC 2019.04.348-.360, FC 2019.04.362-.365, FC 2019.04.367-.373, FC 2019.04.375-.377, FC 2019.04.379, FC 2019.04.381, FC 2019.04.384-.386 (Box 1, Folder Henley-Post & Henderson Co.)
    - Business Documents, O-P, 1905 - 1910; Invoices and receipts from various businesses to Louis Henley. Checks from Henley to various businesses.; Includes items FC 2019.04.389-390, FC 2019.04.395, FC 2019.04.397-400, FC 2019.04.402, FC 2019.04.406-409, FC 2019.04.413-416, FC 2019.04.421-.434, FC 2019.04.437 (Box 1, Folder Henley-O-P)
  - Business Documents Q-S
    - Business Documents, Q-S, 1905 - 1910; Invoices and receipts from various businesses to Louis Henley. Checks from Henley to various businesses.; Includes items FC 2019.04.438-.441, FC 2019.04.447-449, FC 2019.04.453-455, FC 2019.04.461-.467, FC 2019.04.469-470, FC 2019.04.472-474, FC 2019.04.481, FC 2019.04.483-.488, FC 2019.04.490, FC 2019.04.492-493, FC 2019.496, FC 2019.499 (Box 1, Folder Henley-Q-S)
    - Business Documents, Salem Nail Co., 1906; Invoices and receipts from the Salem Nail Co. to Louis Henley. Checks from Louis Henley to the Co.; Includes items FC 2019.04.500-.506 (Box 1, Folder Henley-Salem Nail Co.)
    - Business Documents, Scranton Bolt & Nut Co., 1909; Invoices and bills of lading from the Scranton Bolt & Nut Co. to Louis Henley; Includes items FC 2019.04.509-510, FC 2019.512-.517, FC 2019.04.520-.524 (Box 1, Folder Henley-Scranton Bolt & Nut Co.)
    - Business Documents, Seneca River Power Co., 1908 - 1910; Bills and invoices from the Seneca River Power Co. to Louis Henley.; Includes items FC 2019.04.526-.536, FC 2019.04.538-.551, FC 2019.04.553, FC 2019.04.557-.558, FC 2019.04.561-.562 (Box 1, Folder Henley-Seneca River Power Co.)
    - Business Documents, Standard Oil Co. of New York, 1906 - 1909; Invoices and receipts from the Standard Oil Co. of NY to Louis Henley. Checks from Henley to the Standard Oil Co.; Includes items FC 2019.04.563-.568, FC 2019.04.570-573, FC 2019.04.575, FC 2019.04.585-.586 (Box 1, Folder Henley-Standard Oil Co. of New York)
    - Business Documents, Stewart-Kerbaugh-Shanley Co., 1908; Invoices from Louis Henley to the Stewart-Kerbaugh-Shanley Co.; Includes items FC 2019.04.602, FC 2019.04.629, FC 2019.04.637, FC 2019.04.639, FC 2019.04.646, FC 2019.04.653-.654 (Box 1, Folder Henley-Stewart-Kerbaugh-Shanley Co.)
    - Business Documents, Syracuse Boiler Works, 1906; Invoices and receipts from the Syracuse Boiler Works to Louis Henley. Check from Henley to Syracuse Boiler Works; Includes items FC 2019.04.661-.671 (Box 1, Folder Henley-Syracuse Boiler Works)
    - Business Documents, Syracuse Supply Co., 1906 - 1910; Invoices and receipts from Syracuse Supply Co. to Louis Henley.; Includes items FC 2019.04.672-.674, FC 2019.04.676-.679, FC 2019.04.681-.687 (Box 1, Folder Henley-Syracuse Supply Co.)
  - Business Documents T-Z
    - Business Documents, Weed & Co., 1906 - 1910; Invoices, receipts, and shipping bills from Weed & Co., hardware, to Louis Henley. Checks from Henley to Weed & Co.; Includes items FC 2019.04.697-.712, FC 2019.04.719-.721, FC 2019.04.723-.725, FC 2019.04.728-.731, FC 2019.04.733, FC 2019.04.737-.741, FC 2019.04.745, FC 2019.04.747-.753, FC 2019.04.755-.756 (Box 1, Folder Henley-Weed & Co.)
    - Business Documents, T-Z, 1905 - 1910; Invoices, receipts, and freight bills from various companies to Louis Henley. Checks from Henley to various companies.; Includes items FC 2019.04.758, FC 2019.04.761-.769, FC 2019.04.773-.778, FC 2019.04.780, FC 2019.04.783, FC 2019.04.794-.804 (Box 1, Folder Henley-T-Z)
  - Business Documents Miscellaneous
    - Business Documents, Miscellaneous, 1905 - 1909; Miscellaneous business documents belonging to Louis Henley; Includes items FC 2019.04.809, FC 2019.04.811-.813, FC 2019.04.823-.840, FC 2019.04.846 (Box 1, Folder Henley-Miscellaneous)
  - Business Documents A
    - Business Documents, Atlas Oil Co., 1906 - 1909; Invoices from the Atlas Oil Co. to Louis Henley. Checks from Henley to the Atlas Oil Co.; Includes items FC 2019.04.854-.857, FC 2019.04.859-.862, FC 2019.04.864-.865, FC 2019.04.868-.873, FC 2019.04.875 (Box 2, Folder Henley-Atlas Oil Co.)
    - Business Documents, A, 1905 - 1910; Invoices and receipts from various businesses to Louis Henley. Checks from Henley to various businesses.; Includes items FC 2019.04.876-.877, FC 2019.04.883-.892, FC 2019.04.895, FC 2019.04.900, FC 2019.04.902-.914 (Box 2, Folder Henley-A)
  - Business Documents B
    - Business Documents, E.E. Burleigh, 1906 - 1909; Invoices and receipts from E.E. Burleigh, Hardware and Mill Supplies, to Louis Henley. Checks from Henley to E.E. Burleigh.; Includes items FC 2019.04.931-.951 (Box 2, Folder Henley-E.E. Burleigh)
    - Business Documents, B, 1906 - 1909; Invoices and receipts from various businesses to Louis Henley. Checks from Henley to various businesses.; Includes items FC 2019.04.952-.954, FC 2019.04.956, FC 2019.04.958, FC 2019.04.964-.971, FC 2019.04.973-.976, FC 2019.04.978-.979, FC 2019.04.984-.985, FC 2019.04.987-.989, FC 2019.04.992, FC 2019.04.994-.995 (Box 2, Folder Henley-B)
  - Business Documents C
    - Business Documents, The Clancy Hardware Co., 1905 - 1910; Invoices and receipts from the Clancy Hardware Co. to Louis Henley. Checks from Henley to the Clancy Hardware Co.; Includes items FC 2019.04.996-.1075, FC 2019.04.1078-.1112 (Box 2, Folder Henley-The Clancy Hardware Co.)
    - Business Documents, The Crescent Paper & Machine Co., 1906 - 1909; Invoices from the Crescent Paper & Machine Co. to Louis Henley. Checks from Henley to the Crescent Paper & Machine Co.; Includes items FC 2019.04.1113-.1127 (Box 2, Folder Henley-The Crescent Paper & Machine Co.)
    - Business Documents, C, 1905 - 1910; Invoices and receipts from various businesses to Louis Henley; Includes items FC 2019.04.1128-.1133, FC 2019.04.1140, FC 2019.04.1146-.1148, FC 2019.04.1150-.1151, FC 2019.04.1158, FC 2019.04.1160-.1161 (Box 2, Folder Henley-C)
  - Business Documents D-G
    - Business Documents, DeGrauw, Aymar & Co., 1906 - 1909; Invoices from the DeGrauw, Aymar & Co. to Louis Henley. Checks from Henley to DeGrauw, Aymar & Co.; Includes items FC 2019.04.1166-.1172, FC 2019.04.1174-.1182, FC 2019.04.1189, FC 2019.04.1192, FC 2019.04.1196-.1202 (Box 2, Folder Henley-DeGrauw, Aymar & Co.)
    - Business Documents, D-G, 1905 - 1910; Invoices and receipts from various businesses to Louis Henley. Checks from Henley to various businesses.; Includes items FC 2019.04.1206-.1213, FC 2019.04.1215-.1222, FC 2019.04.1226-.1227, FC 2019.04.1229, FC 2019.04.1231, FC 2019.04.1235-.1244, FC 2019.04.1249, FC 2019.04.1256, FC 2019.04.1259, FC 2019.04.1264-.1266, FC 2019.04.1268, FC 2019.04.1271-.1272, FC 2019.04.1275, FC 2019.04.1278, FC 2019.04.1286-.1289, FC 2019.04.1299 (Box 2, Folder Henley-D-G)
    - Business Documents, Empire Engineering Corp., 1907 - 1909; Invoice from Louis Henley to the Empire Engineering Corp.; Includes item FC 2019.04.1336 (Box 2, Folder Henley-Empire Engineering Corp.)
    - Business Documents, The Fairbanks Co., 1905 - 1910; Invoices and receipts from The Fairbanks Co. to Louis Henley. Checks from Henley to The Fairbanks Co.; Includes items FC 2019.04.1337-.1387, FC 2019.04.1389-.1391, FC 2019.04.1393-.1405, FC 2019.04.1407-.1415, FC 2019.04.1417-.1421, FC 2019.04.1423-.1435, FC 2019.04.1437-.1444, FC 2019.04.1446, FC 2019.04.1448-.1456 (Box 2, Folder Henley-The Fairbanks Co.)
    - Business Documents, Fulton & Phoenix Exchanges, 1909 - 1910; Phone bills from Fulton & Phoenix Exchanges to Louis Henley; Includes items FC 2019.04.1457-.1474 (Box 2, Folder Henley-Fulton & Phoenix Exchanges)
    - Business Documents, D.L. Gillespie & Co., 1909; Invoices from D.L. Gillespie & Co. to Louis Henley.; Includes items FC 2019.04.1480-.1481, FC 2019.04.1483, FC 2019.04.1488-.1489 (Box 2, Folder Henley-D.L. Gillespie & Co.)
- Advertisements
  - Advertisements H-J
    - Advertisements, H-J, Dimensions of 'Imperial' Drills.; Includes item FC 2019.04.36 (Box 1, Folder Henley- H-J)
  - Advertisements K-L
    - Advertisements, K-L, 1908; Product list from Jas. H. Link Machinery Co.; Includes item FC 2019.04.96 (Box 1, Folder Henley-K-L)
  - Advertisements M-N
    - Advertisements, M-N, 1908; Product and price list from the National Lead Company.; Includes item FC 2019.04.266 (Box 1, Folder Henley-M-N)
  - Advertisements O-P
    - Advertisements, O-P, Advertisement for Star Improved Hose Bands; Includes item FC 2019.04.418 (Box 1, Folder Henley-O-P)
  - Advertisements Q-S
    - Advertisements, Q-S, Advertisements for Reeves Roller Thrust Bearing from the Reeves Pulley Co. and E.D. Smalley's Spiral Reinforced Pipe.; Includes items FC 2019.04.443, FC 2019.04.475 (Box 1, Folder Henley-Q-S)
    - Advertisements, Salem Nail Co., Product list from the Salem Nail Co.; Includes items FC 2019.04.507-.508 (Box 1, Folder Henley-Salem Nail Co.)
    - Advertisements, Standard Oil Co. of New York, 1909; Price list from the Standard Oil Co. of New York; Includes item FC 2019.04.574 (Box 1, Folder Henley-Standard Oil Co. of New York)
  - Advertisements T-Z
    - Advertisements, Frank Toomey, Advertisements for wood working machinery and boilers, engines, pumps, heaters, and hoisting engines, sold by Frank Toomey; Includes items FC 2019.04.689-.693 (Box 1, Folder Henley-Frank Toomey)
    - Advertisements, T-Z, Business Card of Wilson Coal & Coke Co. and Price List of The C.A. Woolsey Paint and Color Co. to jobbers only; Includes items FC 2019.04.791, FC 2019.04.793 (Box 1, Folder Henley-T-Z)
  - Advertisements A
    - Advertisements, American Wood Working Machinery Co., 1907; Advertisements for planers and matchers from the American Wood Working Machinery Co.; Includes items FC 2019.04.848-.853 (Box 2, Folder Henley-American Woodworking Machinery Co.)
    - Advertisements, A, 1901; Product list for American Steel & Wire Co. and advertisement for Wickwire Brand Hex Nettings.; Includes items FC 2019.04.896-.897 (Box 2, Folder Henley-A)
  - Advertisements B
    - Advertisements, B, Advertisement for Badger State Machine Co.; Includes item FC 2019.04.955 (Box 2, Folder Henley-B)
  - Advertisements D-G
    - Advertisements, DeGrauw, Aymar & Co., 1906; Advertisement for DeGrauw, Aymar & Co. Cotton Duck and Flax Canvas, and a piece of cotton duck fabric.; Includes items FC 2019.04.1203-.1204 (Box 2, Folder Henley-DeGrauw, Aymar & Co.)
    - Advertisements, D-G, Advertisement for The DuBrie Marine and advertisement for timber planer from Goodell & Waters; Includes items FC 2019.04.1233, FC 2019.04.1298 (Box 2, Folder Henley-D-G)